sciencebasedmedicine.org 2015-06-27

# Privacy Policy « Science-Based Medicine

**Information Collection and Retention**

The only personally identifiable information NESS will collect about you online is information that you voluntarily provide to us. NESS will only use your personally identifiable information to respond to your requests and to provide you with information about NESS’s services, unless we obtain your permission to use your personal information for other purposes. If you contact us regarding employment opportunities, we will collect the information you elect to send us in connection with your request or inquiry and will use the information to match you with available opportunities.

The personally identifiable information you provide to us will be retained only for as long as necessary to fulfill the purposes for which the information was collected or as required by law. We do not share personal information with third parties except as necessary to carry out our business or as required by law or other legal processes, and we never sell your personal information. Unless otherwise required by law, NESS does not identify publicly who sends questions or comments through this website.

NESS automatically collects information regarding visitors’ use of this website without any personal or identifying information. This includes: domain name from which a user accesses the Internet, the date and time and duration user was connected to the website, the Internet address of the website from which a user linked directly to this website, the type of browser used to access this website and the search engine and keywords used when searching for this website. This information is in aggregate to measure website performance.

**Account Identification**  
If any portion of our website requires you to register or open an account, you may also be asked to choose a password and a user name. Please select a password that would not be obvious to someone trying to guess your password, and change it regularly as an added precaution. You are responsible for maintaining the confidentiality of the password and account, and you are fully responsible for all activities that occur under your password or account identification. You agree to immediately notify NESS of any unauthorized use of your password or account or any other breach of security. NESS may rely on the authority of anyone accessing your account or using your password and in no event and under no circumstances will NESS be held liable to you for any liabilities or damages resulting from or arising out of (i) any action or inaction of NESS under this provision, (ii) any compromise of the confidentiality of your account or password and (iii) any unauthorized access to your account or use of your password. You may not use anyone else’s account at any time, without the permission of the account holder.

**Use of Cookies**  
NESS uses “cookies” to help personalize and maximize your online experience and time online. A cookie is a text file that is placed on your hard drive by a web page server. Cookies are not used to run programs or deliver viruses to your computer. Cookies are uniquely assigned to your computer, and can only be read by a web server in the domain that issued the cookie to you.

**Child Protection**  
NESS understands the importance of protecting children’s privacy, especially in an online environment. Our sites are not intentionally designed for or directed at children under the age of 13 years. It is our policy never to knowingly collect or maintain information about anyone under the age of 13.

**Links to Other Websites**  
This website may contain links to other websites. Once you link to another website, you are subject to the privacy policy of the new website.
